Lewis Nathaniel Chase Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General File, 1836-1941 (Box 34-162)
  - Copeland, Charles T., 1928
  - Coppard, Alfred E., 1925-1929, 1936-1939
  - Corfe Castle, undated
  - Conford, Frances, 1935
  - Correspondence, the lost art of, 1921
  - Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C., 1929-1940
  - Costa, A., 1928-1930, 1936
  - Cotton, Charles, 1922
  - Couldrey, Oswald, undated
  - Coup d'etat in Peking, China, 1924
  - Cousins, James H., 1914-1924, 1933
  - Coutts, Francis, 1923-1927
  - Cowley, 1907
  - Cowper, William, 1901-1904, 1928-1932, 1938, (2 folders)
  - Cox, Fay, 1930-1933
  - Crabbe, George, undated
  - Cranage, D. H. S., 1927
  - Crane, Nathalia, 1926-1941
  - Crapsey, Adelaide, 1916-1923, 1931-1937
  - Crashaw, Richard, 1927, 1937-1940
  - Cremation, 1910 (Box 60)
  - Creston, Dormer, 1928
  - Criterion, 1928
  - Criticism, 1912, 1923-1930, (2 folders)
  - Crittenden, 1919-1931
  - Croce, Benedetto, 1922-1924, 1933
  - Cromwell, Oliver, undated
  - Cronin, Patrick, undated
  - Crosby, J. M., 1913, undated
  - Crosland, Thomas William H., 1928
  - Cross, Norman, undated
  - Crowborough, Sussex, 1912
  - Crowell, N. H., 1936
  - Croissant, J. W. C., 1929
  - Crowley, Aleister, 1921, 1929
  - Cuala Press, 1929-1930
  - Cullen, Countee, 1926
  - Culture and democracy, 1924
  - Cummings, E. E., 1935-1939
  - Cummings, Mrs. Robert Fowler, 1926-1937
  - Curiosities, undated
  - Curious phrases, 1928, undated
  - Current Literature, 1906
  - “D” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1910-1917, 1925-1938
    - Miscellany, 1933-1935
    - Newspaper clippings, 1922-1941
  - Dance, 1924-1926
  - Dante, Alighieri, undated (Box 61)
  - Danton, Annina Periam, 1907, 1931, 1940, undated
  - Darby, Louise, 1909-1911
  - Davenant, William, 1935-1939
  - David Copperfield, 1924
  - Davenport, Kirk, 1911-1916
  - Davies, Emil, 1912
  - Davies, William H., 1914, 1922-1940
  - Davis, A. G., 1929
  - Dawson, W., undated
  - Day, Clarence, 1933-1937
  - Deaths for Fiction, undated
  - The Decadents, 1932
  - De Casseres, Benjamin, 1927
  - Defense of the West, 1927
  - Deering, Frank, 1910-1913, 1934-1936
  - Defoe, Daniel, 1907, 1926-1939
  - DeGrassi, Antonio, 1914
  - Dehan, Richard, 1912
  - De Jong, David, 1930-1937
  - De la hunt, 1914
  - De la Mare, Walter, 1916-1940
  - De L'Isle Adam, Villers, 1927 (Box 62)
  - DeMorgan, William, 1939
  - Democratic standards, 1922-1927
  - Depew, Chauncey, undated
  - De Quincey, Thomas, 1907, 1922-1939, (2 folders)
  - Descartes, René, 1926
  - Detroit Fireless Stove Co., 1911, undated
  - Deutsch, Babette, 1936-1940
  - DeVoto, Bernard, 1936, undated
  - Dewey, Georgel, 1899
  - Dewey, Hartley F., 1928
  - Dewey, John, 1929
  - DeWolfe, Jane, 1932-1933
  - Dexter, Byron, 1927
  - Dial, undated
  - The Dialogue, 1926
  - Diarist, eighteenth century, 1923-1924
  - Dickens, Charles, 1899-1904, 1911-1912, 1926-1940, (4 folders)
  - Dickinson, Dorothy, 1914-1915
  - Dickinson, Emily, 1929-1939
  - Dickinson, G. Lowes, undated
  - Dickson, Alice, 1914-1916
  - Dictionary of Anonymous and Pseudonymous English Literature, 1927
  - Dillon, Julia, 1889, undated
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, 1927, 1937
  - Divorce, 1911-1915
  - Dixon, Ella H., undated
  - Dobson, Austin, 1924-1929, 1940 (Box 63)
  - Dodd, William J., 1926
  - Doggerel, 1925
  - Donne's devotions, 1923-1941
  - Do not read for pleasure, 1920
  - Doolittle, H. D. (Hilda), 1924, 1931-1932
  - Dorset, undated
  - Double Dealer, 1926, undated
  - Doughty, Charles, 1926-1939
  - Doughty, George, 1927
  - Douglas, Alfred, 1919, 1928-1940
  - Douglas, Davison McDowell, 1929
  - Douglas, James, 1928
  - Douglas, Lucile, 1935
  - Douglas, Norman, 1928-1930
  - Dow, Allen, 1927
  - Dowie, John Alexander, 1903
  - Drake, Edward, 1934-1937
  - Drama lecture, undated
  - Drama Society, 1913, undated
  - Drama, 1922-1940
  - Drama, one-act plays, 1930
  - Dramatic Advisor, 1924 (Box 64)
  - Dramatic class, 1924
  - Dramatic Principle Story, undated
  - Draper, Warwick H., 1910-1916
  - Dreiser, Theodore, 1911-1912, 1924-1935
  - Drinkwater, John, 1919-1938
  - The Druids, 1927
  - Dryden, John, 1929-1937, undated
  - Dudley, Louise, undated
  - Duhamel, Georges, 1926
  - Duke University, Durham, N.C. (Box 65)
    - 1929-1936, undated, (9 folders)
    - 1930-1935 (Box 66)
  - Dunbar, Paul L., 1914
  - Duncan, Raymond, 1913
  - Duncan, Winifred, 1932
  - Dunsany, Lord, 1916-1940, (3 folders)
  - Durham, N.C., 1930
  - “E” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1907-1940
    - Miscellany, 1927-1933
    - Newspaper clippings, 1924-1940
  - Eames, Wilberforce, 1935-1937
  - Easter, undated
  - Eastwood, Helen, 1895-1899, 1910
  - Eaton, Howard, 1924
  - Economics, 1923-1925
  - Eco-Thermal Co., 1910-1914
  - Eddy, Alfred U., 1935-1936
  - The Editor, 1905-1913 (Box 67)
  - Edman, Irwin, 1926
  - Edson, Philips Josiah, undated
  - Education, 1904-1905, 1920-1937, undated, (4 folders)
  - King Edward VII, 1910
  - Edwards, Frances, 1919-1928, 1936
  - Edwards, Harry Stillwell, 1930-1940
  - Einstein, David Lewis, 1912, 1921, 1934
  - El Centro and Imperial Valley, 1925
  - Elective system, 1904-1905
  - Electric cooker, 1910-1913
  - Electric exhibit, 1910-1913
  - Elegy, 1902
  - Eliot, Charles W., undated (Box 68)
  - Eliot, George, 1899, 1904, 1926, 1935-1941
  - Eliot, Thomas S., 1920-1941
  - Elizabethan drama, 1908-1911, 1924-1925, 1935-1940
  - Elizabethan Stage Society, circa 1912
  - Elizabethan literature, 1928, 1939
  - Elizabethan drama, Chinese students, undated
  - Elks, Benevolent Protective Order of, 1930-1931
  - Ellis, Mrs. Henry Havelock, 1926, undated
  - Elmer, Robert F., 1908-1926
  - Emerson, Frank W., 1936-1937 (Box 69)
  - Enders, Gordon B., 1934-1936
  - Engineer's valuation of English, 1927
  - England, 1911, 1927, undated, (4 folders)
  - Engle, Paul, 1935-1939
  - English association, 1904, 1915-1940, (3 folders)
  - English humor, undated
  - English Inn, 1926
  - English language, 1892, 1906, 1920
  - English literature, 1924-1929
  - English love of nature, undated
  - English, National Council of Teachers of, 1927
  - English, writing of, 1904-1911, (5 folders) (Box 70)
  - English class material
    - 1928-1930, (13 folders) (Box 71)
    - 1928, (11 folders) (Box 72)
  - English prose, 1920, 1926 (Box 73)
  - English, pure, 1919-1928
  - English, Romantic period, 1926
  - English verse, speaking association, 1928-1929
  - English student, 1923-1928, (3 folders)
  - English, teachings of, 1913, 1919-1922, 1938
  - English traits, 1913
  - English vocabulary, Inglis test of, undated
  - Ensor, Robert Charles Kirkwood, 1922-1925
  - L'Entente Cordiale, 1909-1910
  - Enunciation exercises, undated
  - Epigrams, undated
  - Epitaphs, 1927
  - Epitholam, undated
  - Erasmus, Desiderius, 1906, 1922-1924
  - Erskine, John, 1936-1940
  - Essays, 1904-1905, 1922-1927, (6 folders) (Box 74)
  - Etherege, George, 1925-1928
  - Ethridge, Willie Snow, 1929, 1937-1941
  - Etiquette, 1928
  - Europe, 1912
  - Evans, Alexander William, 1911-1914
  - Evans, Edward, 1923-1924
  - Evelyn, John, 1937-1940
  - Everard, Welby, undated
  - Everyman's Library, undated
  - Everyman magazine, 1912
  - Evolution, 1925
  - Examination questions, 1917-1928, (5 folders)
  - Exam paper, samples, 1924-1929
  - Express water boiler, 1914-1915
  - “F” miscellaneous (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, 1906-1915, 1927-1940
    - Miscellany, 1911-1914, 1921-1933
    - Newspaper clippings, 1920-1939
  - Falstaff, 1923
  - Farnham, 1911
  - Farquhar, George, 1915
  - Farrand, Max, undated
  - Fawcet, L., undated
  - Ferguson, Ella, 1911-1916
  - Few, William P., 1929-1931, 1940
  - Ficke, Arthur D., 1927
  - Fiction, 1922-1927
  - Field, Eugene, 1930, 1936
  - Field, Michael, 1919-1924
  - Field genealogy, 1934-1935
  - Fielding, Henry, 1919
  - Fischer, Ernst Georg, 1934-1935
  - Fish, 1933, undated
  - Fisk Teachers' Agency, 1905-1906, 1925-1928
  - Fitch, Clyde, undated (Box 76)
  - Fitch, Florence, 1930-1941
  - Fitzgerald, Edward, 1926, undated
  - Flanner, Hidegarde, 1926
  - Flecker, James Elroy, 1913-1938
  - Fletcher, John Gould, 1918, 1924-1941
  - Fletcher, Phineas, undated
  - Flies, 1911-1912
  - Flower, Robin, undated
  - Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, D. C., 1935
  - Folklore and fairy tales for children, 1924-1926, 1935
  - Folkers, Hans and Lily, 1912-1914, 1926-1938
  - Food values, 1911
  - Foot, Constance M., 1911-1912
  - Ford, Ford Madox, 1932-1939
  - Foreign Press Service, 1921
  - Form in art, 1900-1906
  - Forster, E. M., 1924-1927, 1936-1941
  - Forsyth, Jessie, 1911-1914
  - Foster Hall Bulletin, 1940 (Box 77)
  - Fowler, Marie Washburn, 1927
  - Fox, Moireen, undated
  - France
    - Moving to, 1907-1910
    - Postcards, 1909
    - Rough notes, 1909-1911
  - France, Anatole, 1925
  - Franck, Harry A., 1925-1926
  - Frank, Waldo, 1922-1924
  - Franklin, Benjamin, 1922-1939
  - Frazer, James, 1923, 1940-1941
  - Freedom, 1919
  - Freeman, John, 1919, 1936
  - Free verse, 1924-1926
  - Free woman, 1912
  - French, undated
  - French plays catalogue, 1899-1900
  - French romantics, 1926-1927
  - Freshman English, Union College, Schenectady, N.Y., 1927-1928
  - Frost, Elizabeth H., 1935, undated
  - Frost, Frances, 1931-1940
  - Frost, Robert, 1923-1941, (2 folders)
  - Furnishings, 1910
  - Furniture, 1927-1928, 1934
  - Furniture catalogue, undated
  - Furniture, humanly speaking, undated
  - “G” miscellaneous (Box 78)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1940
    - Miscellany, 1908, 1928-1936
    - Newspaper clippings, 1923-1926, 1933-1939
  - Gaff, Mary, 1910-1914
  - Gale, Norman, 1914-1918, undated
  - Galsworthy, John, 1911-1912, 1924-1939
  - Gammons, Harold, 1932
  - Gandhi, Mohandas K., 1920-1923, 1934
  - Gap between home and college, undated
  - Garden suburbs, 1908-1913
  - Garnett, David, 1923
  - Garrard, Lindsay, 1926
  - Garrick, David, 1906
  - Garrod, Heathcote W., 1936
  - Gartz, Kate Crane, 1923-1926
  - Gas ranges, 1914 (Box 79)
  - Gascoigne, G., undated
  - Gaskell, Elizabeth, undated
  - Gaunt, Mary, 1911
  - Gautier, E., 1912-1913
  - Gay, John, 1938
  - Geil, William Edgar, 1925, 1940
  - General Steam Navigation Co., 1910
  - Geniaux, Charles, 1912-1913
  - George III, King, 1928
  - George, Dorothy, 1928
  - George, Henry, 1931-1933
  - Georgetown College, Washington, D.C., 1929
  - Gerhardi, William, 1926-1938
  - Germain, Andre, 1911
  - Gerould, Katharine Fullerton, 1926
  - Gibbon, Monk, 1926-1937
  - Gibbs, John, 1931
  - Gibson, Wilfred Wilson, 1917, 1924-1934
  - Gide, Andre, 1920
  - Gifford, Alfred, 1923-1925
  - Gilbert, James J., 1931
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, undated
  - Gillette, Ruth, 1921-1934
  - Gillette, William, 1937
  - Ginn and Co., 1928
  - National Organization of Girls' Clubs, 1911-1912
  - Glasson, W. H., 1932-1933
  - Godbey, Allen H., 1930
  - Goethe, 1920-1932
  - Goette, John Andrew, 1921-1929, 1937
  - Gogarty, Oliver St. John, 1937-1940 (Box 80)
  - The Golden Bough, 1922-1924
  - The Golden Treasury, 1917, undated
  - Goldsmith, 1924-1928
  - Gollancz, Herman, 1923, 1941
  - Goncourt, Edmond and Jules, 1928
  - Good Housekeeping, 1912
  - Good resolutions die young, 1906
  - Good sentences in student reports, undated
  - Gore, Percy, 1912-1913
  - Gore-Booth, Eva, 1929
  - Gorell, Lord, 1934-1941
  - Gorst, 1941
  - Gosse, Edmund, 1912-1915, 1925-1938
  - Gould, Gerald, 1927-1930
  - Gourion, Je, 1912-1914
  - Graham, Stephen, 1923-1924
  - Graham, Cunninghame, 1920, 1929-1932
  - Grammar, 1930
  - Grant, Harry L, 1933-1935
  - Grantham, A. E., 1934-1938
  - Graves, Alfred Percival, 1913
  - Graves, Robert, 1919-1941
  - Gray, Alexis Stuart, 1911
  - Gray, Thomas, 1925-1928, 1937
  - Grayhound Press, 1927
  - Grayson, Marguerete, 1926-1928
  - Greaves, Winifred, 1911-1913
  - Greek point of view, 1940, undated
  - Green, Paul, 1939
  - Green, A. Romney, 1913-1915, 1927, (2 folders)
  - Greene's Library, 1927-1929
  - Greene, W. K., 1930-1931
  - Greenleaf, 1933 (Box 81)
  - Greenslet, Ferris, 1901-1906
  - Gregory, Lady, 1930-1931
  - Grenfell, Julian, undated
  - Grenoble, Universite de Grenoble, France, 1900-1909
  - Gretton, M. Sturge, 1922
  - Grey, Pamela, 1923
  - Grierson, Francis, 1910-1912, 1927, (2 folders)
  - Grierson, H. J. C., undated
  - Grocers
    - Edourd Robinson and Co., 1910-1913
    - Gage and Strobek, 1928-1929
  - Guedalla, Philip, 1933
  - Guest book, 1901
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1927-1928
  - Guest, Flora Bigelow, 1919
  - Guilford, undated
  - Guistler, Elsa, 1912-1915
  - Guiney, Louise Imogen, 1923, 1938
  - Gwynn, Stephen, 1926
  - Gypsies, 1926
  - “H” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1894, 1914-1940
    - Miscellany, 1907, 1930-1938
    - Newspaper clippings, 1921-1944
  - Haanel, Charles F., 1919-1926
  - Halcyon Club, 1913 (Box 82)
  - Haldane, Viscount, 1926
  - Hale, Edward E., undated
  - Hale, Edward, 1903-1905, 1925-1932, (2 folders)
  - Hall, James Norman, 1916-1922, 1936-1942
  - Hall, Harvey P., 1929
  - Hall, Percival, 1935-1936
  - Hallenbeck, E., 1927-1929
  - Halliburton, Richard, 1935-1940
  - Hamid Ali Khan, 1921
  - Hamilton, Clive, 1927
  - Hamilton, George Rostrevor, 1924-1941, (2 folders)
  - Hammersmith, London, England, 1909-1917, (8 folders)
  - Hammond typewriter, 1912-1914 (Box 83)
  - Hamon, M. Augustin, 1911
  - Hampshire House Club, 1909-1917, (6 folders)
  - Hampstead, 1912
  - Hannum, Louise, 1925-1927
  - Hanson, Frank, 1911-1914
  - Hanson, Howard, 1935
  - Hapgood, Norman, 1937 (Box 84)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Co., 1926-1928
  - Harding, H. I., 1922
  - Hardy, Edward, 1925-1927
  - Hardy, Thomas, 1914, 1922-1944
  - Harlow, S. Ralph, 1922
  - Harper's Publishing Co., 1927
  - Harraden, Beatrice, 1936
  - Harrap, George, 1911-1915, 1921-1932
  - Harris, Joel Chandler, 1931
  - Harrison, Marguerite, 1907, 1925
  - Harrison, Thomas P., 1929
  - Harrow on the Hill, 1911
  - Hart, Henry H., 1936-1937
  - Hart, Walter M., 1926-1927
  - Harte, Bret, 1922-1936
  - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 1931-1937
  - Harvey, F. W., 1917 (Box 85)
  - Harvey, Paul, 1926
  - Haultain, Arnold, 1908
  - Hauptmann, Gerhart, 1919
  - Havens, Raymond, 1929
  - Hawkins, G. Addington, and family, 1912-1914
  - Hawthorne, Nathaniel, 1906, 1941, undated, (2 folders)
  - Hawthorne Inn and Cottages, 1935-1936
  - Haydon, Benjamin Robert, 1928
  - Hays, Alice, 1934
  - Hays, Clara, 1923, 1941, undated
  - Haywood, E. H., 1914-1915
  - Hazlitt, William, 1922, 1924, 1935
  - Healey, Richard E. H., 1912-1913
  - Hearn, Lafcadio, 1923, 1931-1940
  - Hearst, William Randolph, 1935
  - Hedges, James B., 1936
  - Hedin, Sven, 1926, 1933-1940
  - Heise, John, 1936-1938
  - Henderson, Archibald, 1931-1935
  - Henry, Mellinger Edward, 1934-1938
  - Henshaw, Joh, 1932-1935
  - Herbert, Goerge, 1905-1906
  - Herdmean, Hugh H., 1907, 1933-1934
  - Herendeen, Frederick, 1934-1936
  - Herodotus, 1924 (Box 86)
  - Heroic Spirit, 1927
  - Herrick, Robert, 1912, 1921, 1927-1929
  - Herron, George D., 1932
  - Hewes, Charles Edwin, 1933
  - Hewlett, Maurice, 1917-1926, 1933, 1943
  - Higgins, F. R., 1928, 1940
  - Hill, Louis, 1908-1911
  - Hill, William H, 1933
  - Hillyer, Robert, 1926-1943
  - Hilton, James, 1931, 1938-1939
  - Hindu nights, 1925
  - Hinduism, 1928
  - Hinton, James, 1929
  - Hints to those about to travel, undated
  - History, 1919, 1925-1928
  - Hobbs, Mary, 1912
  - Hocking, Samuel, 1926-1930
  - Hodges, Margaret, 1932-1938
  - Hodgson, Ralph, 1914-1933, (4 folders)
  - Hoeing, Charles, 1925-1938
  - Hogarth Press, circa 1927
  - Hogue, Richard and Caroline, 1931-1940
  - Holbrook, Antoinette, 1925-1937
  - Holbrook, Weare, 1928
  - Holbrook, William and Roscoe D., 1925, 1933
  - Holgate, Eleanor, undated (Box 87)
  - Holland, G. C. F., 1924
  - Hollis, Howard, 1901, 1924-1938
  - Hollywood Book Shop, 1927
  - Holme, Constance, 1926
  - Holmes, Edmond, 1936
  - Holmes, John, 1935-1940
  - Holyland, Carrie E., 1932
  - Holyoke's New Plan, 1935
  - Hong Kong and Shanghai Banking Corp., 1925
  - Honor man's dilemma, 1922-1931
  - Honolulu, T. H. undated
  - Hood, Charles Newton, 1908-1910
  - Hopkins, Gerard Manley, 1935-1938
  - Horton, Marion, undated
  - Houghton-Mifflin and Co., 1906
  - Household, the conduct of, 1923
  - Housman, A. E., 1926-1943, (3 folders)
  - Housman, Laurence, 1911, 1923-1930, 1941, (2 folders)
  - Hovey, Richard, 1909, 1936 (Box 88)
  - How to become an author, 1927
  - How to read aloud, 1926, undated, (2 folders)
  - How to study the poetry of Gray and Goldsmith, undated
  - How to teach poetry in war times, undated
  - Howard, Robert, undated
  - Howe, John B. And Eva, 1932-1938
  - Howell, B. R., 1911-1915, 1933-1935
  - Howells, William Dean, 1916, 1923-1925
  - Hubble, Edwin, 1921, 1931-1936, (2 folders)
  - Hudson, William Henry, 1910-1914, 1922-1924, (2 folders)
  - Hueffer, Violet Hunt, 1913-1914
  - Hughes, John, undated
  - Hughes, Richard, 1923-1925
  - The human element in education, 1919, undated., (2 folders)
  - Human testimony, 1921
  - Humanitarian movement, 1923
  - Humber, Robert Lee, 1921-1930
  - Hummel, Arthur, 1925-1928, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
  - Hunt, Hazel, 1927-1929
  - Hunt, Leigh, 1927, undated
  - Huntington, E., 1914, 1925-1928, (2 folders)
  - Husain, Mazhar, 1921 (Box 89)
  - Husain, S. R., 1921
  - Hu Shih, 1923-1925, 1931-1942
  - Hutcherson, Grover, 1907-1912
  - Hutchinson and Co., 1912-1915
  - Huxley, Aldous, 1922-1931
  - Hyde, Douglas, 1938
  - Hymns, undated
  - Hymn writing, 1926
  - Hypnotism, 1905
  - “I” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1906, 1914-1915, 1929-1934
    - Miscellany, 1900, 1913, 1928, 1935
    - Newspaper clippings, 1922-1938
  - Ibsen Henrik, 1912, 1921-1928
  - The idol, 1929
  - Igleheart, Eleanor, 1908-1918, 1925
  - Imagery, 1927 (Box 90)
  - Imagination and intellect, 1926, 1936
  - Income tax, 1910-1915, 1928-1938, (3 folders)
  - India, 1919-1939, (11 folders)
  - Indian symbols, undated (Box 91)
  - Indian village tragedies, 1920
  - Indiana University, Bloomington, Ind., 1903-1905, 1923-1925, 1934, (2 folders)
  - Industrialism, 1924-1926
  - Inge, William Ralph, 1919, 1927
  - Ingersoll, Louise, 1933-1938
  - Ingersoll, Robert, 1888, 1933-1934
  - Inglis, Alexander, 1926-1928
  - Ingraham, Isabel and Ruth, 1938-1939
  - Inspiration, 1931
  - Instinct, 1926
  - Insurance, 1910-1915, 1933
  - Interior decoration, 1908-1910
  - International Banking Corp., 1925
  - Invalid kitchens of London, England, 1910
  - Invitations of lecture, 1926-1928
  - Ireland, 1912, 1917, 1925-1932 (Box 92)
  - Ireland mementos, 1927, 1935-1937
  - Ireland's literature, 1927-1929, 1935-1941
  - Irish poetry, 1930
  - Irish statesman, 1930
  - Irish views and post cards, 1927-1928, undated
  - Irvine, Scotland, postcards, undated
  - Irving, Henry, 1903-1905, 1938-1939
  - Irving, Washington, 1925
  - Islam, 1932 (Box 93)
  - Ison, Henry Halford, 1912-1914
  - Italy, 1927
  - “J” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1907-1916, 1926-1932
    - Miscellany, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1927-1938
  - Jackson, A. V. Williams, 1903-1906, 1935-1937
  - Jacob, Sophia, 1925
  - James, Henry, undated
  - Japan, 1920-1938, (10 folders)
  - Jaqua, Ernest James, undated
  - Jastrow, Joseph, 1919
  - Jeffers, Robinson, 1926-1941
  - Jefferson, Thomas, and Alexander Hamilton, 1926
  - Jenkins, Charles, 1909-1915, 1922
  - Jepson, Melvin, 1932-1938 (Box 94)
  - Jesus, 1930
  - Jesus and Mencius, 1926, undated
  - Jillson, Harriet, 1931-1934
  - Joad, C. E. M., 1926-1928
  - Johnson, Isabel, 1926
  - Johnson, Lionel, 1911
  - Johnson, Samuel, 1926-1931, 1937-1940
  - Johnston, H. W., 1901-1906
  - Johnston, Reginald F., 1932-1938
  - Joker, undated
  - Jokes, 1927
  - Jones, Pamelia Pearl, 1927
  - Jones, Thomas, 1929-1936
  - Jonson, Ben, 1906, 1919, 1925-1927, 1936-1937
  - Josselin, 1909
  - Jottings from Japan, 1919, undated
  - Journalism, undated
  - Joyce, Horace F., 1911-1915
  - Joyce, James, 1933-1941
  - Judy, Clinton, 1925-1929
  - “K” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1907-1915, 1923-1934
    - Miscellany, 1916, 1935, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1927-1939
  - Kabir, Humayun, 1932, undated
  - Kahn, Gustave, 1936 (Box 95)
  - Kalevala, undated
  - Kashmir, 1925
  - Kastendieck, Carroll, 1917
  - Kaufman, Herbert, 1918
  - Keating, John A., 1894-1898, 1926
  - Keats, John, 1905, 1911-1914, 1922-1939
  - Keen, C. Colvin, 1913-1915
  - Kellam, Etta, 1894, 1902-1906, (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - Keller, Inez Rice, 1912
  - Kellett, E. E., undated (Box 97)
  - Kellogg, Charles, 1926
  - Kelmscott house, undated
  - Kemp, Harry, undated
  - Kentucky summer resorts, 1907
  - Kenyon, Theda, 1929
  - Kenyon College, Gambier, Ohio, 1903
  - Keppel, Mark, 1925
  - Kern, George, 1928
  - Keyserling, Count Hermann, 1928-1930
  - Killelea, J. J., 1910-1912
  - Killigrew, undated
  - Kilmer, Aline, 1919
  - Kilmer, Joyce, 1916-1917, 1930-1939
  - Kipling, Rudyard, 1908, 1923-1928, 1936-1940
  - Kirby, Elizabeth, 1917
  - Kline, Ben, 1925-1926
  - Kodak, 1910-1913, (2 folders)
  - Kolb, Merle, 1919
  - Komai, T., 1914
  - Konig, A., 1910-1915
  - Koodlach, Abraham, 1925 (Box 98)
  - Kraus, Horatio, 1904-1906, 1911
  - Kreckman, Henry Franklin, 1928-1935, (2 folders)
  - “L” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1907-1914, 1926-1941
    - Miscellany, 1906, 1925-1934
    - Newspaper clippings, 1924-1938
  - Labia, Arline, 1908-1913
  - Lacaussade, 1910-1913
  - Laconics, 1928
  - Lacy, undated
  - Laing, B. M., 1922-1923
  - Lang, G. A., 1928
  - Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, Ill., 1906
  - Lake poets, 1898-1900, 1936
  - Lamb, Charles, 1898, 1906, 1939-1940
  - Lampson, Godfrey Locker, 1920, 1932-1934
  - Landi, Zanardi, 1914
  - Landor, Walter Savage, 1927-1928, 1937
  - Lane, John, 1927-1928
  - Lang, Andrew, undated
  - Lantern slides, catalogs, 1927, undated
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1928-1941
  - Laundress, undated (Box 99)
  - Lawrence, D. H., 1919-1940
  - Lawson, Jessie K., 1903-1911
  - Leacock, Stephen, 1932-1940
  - Leaf, Earl H., 1932
  - Leaf, Walter, 1922
  - Lear, Edward, 1938-1939
  - Lease, 1910
  - Le Bourhis, Francis, 1913-1916
  - Le Breton, Andre, 1912, undated
  - Lebus, H., 1910-1911
  - Lecture material, 1902-1907, (3 folders)
  - Le Doux, Louis, 1925, 1935, undated
  - Ledwidge, Francis, 1914-1936, (5 folders)
  - Lee, Alan W. Simms, undated (Box 100)
  - Lee, Gerald Stanley, 1919
  - Lee, H. O., 1921
  - Lee, Sydney, undated
  - Lee Memorial Mission, 1921
  - Legality versus morality, 1925-1926
  - Le Gallienne, Richard, 1915, 1938
  - Leib, Caroline, 1908-1913
  - Leisure, 1918, 1926
  - Leonard, William Ellery, 1917, 1926, 1935-1937
  - Leopardi, Giacomo, 1923-1927, 1937
  - Leslie, Shane, 1931-1934
  - Lester family letters, 1931-1941, (2 folders)
  - Le Strange, Guy, undated
  - Letts, W. M., 1913 (Box 101)
  - Lewis, Arthur A., 1932-1940
  - Lewis, C. Day, 1935-1941
  - Lewis, Sinclair, 1927-1936
  - Lewis, Wyndham, 1927-1933
  - Lewisohn, Ludwig, 1936-1939
  - Lewisohn, Will, 1923-1927, 1940, undated, (4 folders)
  - Libraries, 1924-1933
  - Library of Congress, 1931-1941
  - Lighthouse keeper, 1911
  - Limericks, 1924-1928
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1913-1914, 1928-1936 (Box 102)
  - Lincoln, I., 1935
  - Lincoln, Joseph C., undated
  - Lindley, Francis, 1926
  - Lindsey, Ben B., 1928
  - Lindsay, Vachel, 1914-1936, (2 folders)
  - Linn, E. W., 1918
  - Literary agencies, 1905-1906
  - Literary criticism, 1906, 1930, undated
  - Literary technique, 1922-1934
  - Literary yearbook, 1913-1914, 1932, (2 folders)
  - Literature, 1898-1908, 1921, 1930,undated, (10 folders) (Box 103)
  - Little, Brown and Co., 1917-1919
  - Lloyd, Betram, undated
  - Locke, Audrey, 1917
  - Lockwood, Mary, 1932-1940
  - Little, A. P., 1897
  - Living in France on $1000, undated
  - London, England (Box 104)
    - 1903-1927, (11 folders)